http://www.troopcrew405.org/privacy

Search
Privacy Policy
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the https://codecampopenlabs.com and TroopTrackHQ, LLC and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to TroopTrackHQ, LLC include https://codecampopenlabs.com and TroopTrack. The TroopTrack website is a information and ecommerce site. By using the TroopTrack website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
TroopTrack may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase TroopTrack's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. TroopTrack may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by TroopTrack. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the TroopTrack website.
TroopTrack encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from TroopTrack so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. TroopTrack is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the TroopTrack website.
Use of your Personal Information
TroopTrack collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.
TroopTrack may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from TroopTrack and its affiliates. TroopTrack may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
TroopTrack does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
TroopTrack may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to TroopTrack, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
TroopTrack may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within TroopTrack, in order
to determine what TroopTrack services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within TroopTrack to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
TroopTrack will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on TroopTrack or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of TroopTrack; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of TroopTrack, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The TroopTrack website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize TroopTrack pages, or register with TroopTrack site or services, a cookie helps TroopTrack to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same TroopTrack website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the TroopTrack features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the TroopTrack services or websites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
TroopTrack secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.
Children Under Thirteen
TroopTrack may be used by its customers to collect personally identifiable
information from children under the age of thirteen. It is the
responsibility of the customer to ensure that parents of children grant
permission to collect and use this information. TroopTrack recommends that
customers that collect information about children under 13 copy parents on
all communication to these children. TroopTrack collects this information
for the following reason(s): to track their progress in scouting and to
facilitate communication with their parents about scouting activities.
If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website. If you are a parent and you have questions regarding our data collection practices, please contact us using the information provided at the end of this Statement of Privacy.
Opt-Out & Unsubscribe
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from TroopTrack by contacting us here:
Email: hello@trooptrack.com
Changes to this Statement
TroopTrack will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. TroopTrack encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how TroopTrack is protecting your information.
Contact Information
TroopTrack welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that TroopTrack has not adhered to this Statement, please contact TroopTrack at:
TroopTrackHQ, LLC
2889 Marrcrest W
Provo UT 84604
Email Address: hello@trooptrack.com
Effective as of February 27, 2016
